Carmen McRae Collection of Musical Arrangements and Other Materials
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1931-1976 (Box 1-40)
  - Evil gal blues, Leonard Feather; Lead sheet (Box-folder 5/31)
  - Evil ways, Clarence Henry; Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 5/32)
  - Exactly like you, Jimmy McHugh / Dorothy Fields; Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, organ, double bass, drums); Arranged by Alan Faust (Box-folder 27/6)
  - The eyes of lovers, J. Wallowitch / Tony Scibetta; Lead sheet (Box-folder 5/33)
  - Fade, Nat Adderley, Jr., / Carolyn Plummer; Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Fair weather friend, Doris Fisher / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/2)
  - Falling in love with love, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, double bass) (missing piano, drums); Arranged by Ernie Wilkins; Small group #98 (Box-folder 28/1)
  - Far more blue see Brubeck folder, Dave Brubeck; Lyric sheet
  - Faraway forever, Alan Bergman / Marilyn Bergman / Quincy Jones; Lead sheet and parts (vocal, harp, piano, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Roger Kellaway (Box-folder 6/3)
  - Feeling good, Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #188 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - Flamingo, Parts (vocal, trumpet, horn 1-4, tenor saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar); Arranged by Ralph Burns (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Fly away (whisky love), John Wallowitch / Tony Scibetta; Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Flying, Jerry Leiber / Mike Stoller; Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 34/6)
  - Flying, Jerry Leiber / Mike Stoller; Score; Arranged by Johnny Keating (Box-folder 39/2)
  - Folks who live on the hill, Jerome Kern; Drum part; Small group #373 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Fools and lovers, Cliff Adams / Veronica Barnes; Score and parts (vocal, trumpet, horn 1-4, woodwinds, harp, guitar, percussion, strings); Arranged by Don Sebesky (Box-folder 28/2)
  - For all we know, Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, flute, clarinet 1-4, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by John Clayton (Box-folder 6/8)
  - For once in my life, Ron Miller / Orlando Murden; Score and parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, piano/conductor, guitar, baritone saxophone, double bass, drums); Arranged by Johnny Keating; Small group #345 (Box-folder 6/9)
  - For once in my life, Ron Miller / Orlando Murden; Parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 6/10)
  - For once in my life, Ron Miller / Orlando Murden; Parts (vocal, trombone 1-2, horn 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, harp, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings) (Box-folder 6/11)
  - For once in my life, Ron Miller / Orlando Murden; Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/12)
  - Forget it, Johnny Wayne; Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/13)
  - Forget me, Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #82; On verso of drum part: drum part for "Teach me" #89. (Box-folder 6/14)
  - Fred, Neal Hefti / Sammy Cahn; Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/15)
  - Freddie's walkin', Chuck Mangione; Score sketch (Box-folder 6/16)
  - Free again, Guitar part (Box-folder 6/17)
  - Free and easy, Bobby Troup / Henry Mancini; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 6/18)
  - From now on, Charles Lazar; Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/19)
  - From now on, Don Newey; Lead sheet (Box-folder 6/20)
  - Gee, ain't I good to you, Andy Razaf / Don Redman; Lyric sheet (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Gentleman friend, Score and parts (production, vocal, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, horn 1-4, tuba, woodwinds 1-4, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion 1-2); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #180 (Box-folder 39/3)
  - Gentleman friend, Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #180 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Georgia Rose, Score and vocal lead (Box-folder 28/3)
  - Gertrude Lawrence [medley], Score, vocal lead sheet; Titles: Love of my own; He is something wonderful; Getting to know you; Hello young lovers; "Something wonderful" recording - salute to women of Broadway (Box-folder 38/4)
  - Get out of your cave, Joáo Donato / Mercedes Chies; Vocal/guitar part (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Getting some fun, Piano part (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Ghost of yesterday, Guitar part; Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #287 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Glad there's you, Guitar part; Small group #163 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - Gloomy Sunday, Parts (vocal, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #371 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - Go and buy yourself a dream, Score and parts (vocal group, piano 1-2, drums, percussion) (missing double bass part); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #321 (Box-folder 28/4)
  - God bless the child, Parts (guitar, double bass); Small group #243 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Golden things, Christine Gardner; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Gonna lock my heart, Parts (piano, guitar); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group # 128 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Good bait, Tad Dameron; Lyric sheet and parts (tenor saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 7/11)
  - The good life, Tad Dameron; Lead sheet; Arranged by Manny Album (Box-folder 7/12)
  - A good man, Joan Kraft / Billy Valentine; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/13)
  - A good man is a seldom thing, Charles DeForest; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/14)
  - Good reviews, Lyric sheet (Box-folder 7/15)
  - A good thing, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Goodbye Joe, Kenneth S. Webb / Harold Levey; Score and parts (horn 1-2, woodwinds 1-2, bassoon, piano/guitar, double bass, drums, percussion); Arranged by Arif Mardin (Box-folder 34/7)
  - Goodbye Joe, Kenneth S. Webb / Harold Levey; Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #411 (Box-folder 7/17)
  - Got to get you into my life, Lennon / McCartney; Score and parts (conductor, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, horn, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion); Arranged by Johnny Keating (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Got to get you into my life, Lennon / McCartney; Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons (Box-folder 28/5)
  - Got to get you into my life, Lennon / McCartney; Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #198 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - Groove merchant, Jerome Richardson / John Hendricks; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/20)
  - Guess I'll hang my tears out to dry, Jule Styne / Sammy Cahn; Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #291 (Box-folder 7/21)
  - Guess I'm the last example of the blues, Robert Brann; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/22)
  - Guess who I saw today, Murray Grand / Elisse Boyd; Lead sheet; double bass part; Small group #83 (Box-folder 7/23)
  - Gypsies in the wind, Bob Williams; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/24)
  - Gypsy man, Lead sheet; lyric sheet (Box-folder 7/25)
  - A handful a' soul, Dusko Gojkovic / Jimmy Woode; Score and parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone 1-3, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Francy Boland (Box-folder 7/26)
  - The happy ones, Bob Friedman; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/27)
  - Have a happy, Jerry Goldstone / Johnny Rotella; Lead sheet (Box-folder 7/28)
  - Have a heart, Johnny Mercer / Gene DiNovi; Lead sheet; Laid in: note from Gene DiNovi to Carmen (Box-folder 7/29)
  - Haven't we met, Score and parts (vocal, trumpet, horn 1-4, piccolo flute, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #172 (Box-folder 28/6)
  - Haven't we met, Parts (conductor, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxohpone, flute 1-4, mellophone, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 7/30)
  - Haven't we met, Parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor/guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons (Box-folder 7/31)
  - He loves me, Score and parts (conductor, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, horn 1-4, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, tuba, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion); Arranged by Don Sebesky; Small group #182 (Box-folder 39/4)
  - He loves me, Score and parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, flute, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Johnny Keating (Box-folder 28/7)
  - He loves me, Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, voc/double bass/guitar, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons (Box-folder 28/8)
  - He loves me, Parts (alto saxophone 1-2, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #182 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - He was too good to me, Richard Rodgers / Lorena Hart; Score and parts (production, vocal, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Small group #181 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Heart of my heart, Hugo Montenegro; Alto saxophone part (Box-folder 8/3)
  - The heart you stole from me, Leonard Feather; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Heartless, Bernice Ross / Marian McPartland; Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Heat wave, Irving Berlin; Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Heaven's doors are open wide, Tad Dameron; Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Here it is again Christmas, Ronnell Bright; Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Here near me, Joáo Donato / Norman Grimbel; Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Here, there and everywhere, John Lennon / Paul McCartney; Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #379 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Here's that rainy day, Jimmy Van Heusen; Sketch, parts (vocal, piano/conductor); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Here's to my lover, Neal Hefti; Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Hey John, Parts (piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Hi-fly, John Hendricks / Randy Weston; Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/14)
  - His eye is on the sparrow, Civilla D. Martin / Charles H. Gabri; Score and parts (conductor/vocal, piano/guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Ralph Burns (Box-folder 29/1)
  - Hotel, Score and parts (vocal, trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, flute, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Johnny Keating (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Hotel, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #339 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - How could I settle for less?, R. I. Allen / Sacha Distel; Lead sheets; Arranged by Manny Album (Box-folder 8/17)
  - How did he look, Parts (piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #281 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - How do you like your love?, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 8/19)
  - How does the wine taste?, Parts (vocal, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Marty Paich (Box-folder 8/20)
  - How high the moon / Smoke gets in your eyes, Nancy Hamilton / Morgan Lewis / Jerome Kern / Otto Harbach; Lead sheet (chords) (Box-folder 8/21)
  - How little we know, Carolyn Leigh / Philip Springer; Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Ernie Wilkins; Small group #88 (Box-folder 29/2)
  - How long, Piano part; Small group #137 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - I ain't here, Lyric sheet; parts (master rhythm, vocal); Arranged by Roger Kellaway (Box-folder 9/1)
  - I am music, Parts (vocal, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Roger Kellaway (Box-folder 9/2)
  - I can let go now, Sketch (Box-folder 9/3)
  - I can't explain, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #323 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - I can't get you out of my mind, Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/5)
  - I can't get started with you, Vernon Duke; Lyric sheet, double bass part; Small group #3 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - I can't look away from you, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/7)
  - I can't say no (to the bossa nova), Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/8)
  - I concentrate on you, Cole Porter; Double bass parts; Small group #193 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - I could write a book, Lorenz Hart / Richard Rodgers; Parts (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #28 (Box-folder 9/10)
  - I couldn't care less, Jimmy Van Heusen / Sammy Cahn; Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano); Arranged by Ernie Wilkins (Box-folder 29/3)
  - I cried for you, Arthur Freed / Gus Arnheim / Abe Lyman; Score and parts (conductor, trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #132 (Box-folder 34/8)
  - I didn't know 'til you told me, Dave Brubeck; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/11)
  - I didn't know what time it was, Parts (guitar, drums); Small group #110 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - I didn't see you, Ronnell L. Bright / Sammy Cahn; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/13)
  - I don't want nothin' from nobody, Jimmy Woode / Kenny Clarke; Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Francy Boland (Box-folder 9/14)
  - I fall in love too easily, Jule Styne / Sammy Cahn; Parts (piano, double bass) (Box-folder 9/15)
  - I feel alive again, Lead sheet; On p. 2: note from copyist Hamish Menzies to Carmen McRae (Box-folder 9/16)
  - I get a kick out of you, Cole Porter; Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #54 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - I get along without you, Lead sheet, sketch; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/18)
  - I got it bad[, and that ain't good], Parts (piano, guitar, double bass); Small group #265 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - I have the feeling I've been here before, Alan Bergman / Marilyn Bergman; Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, clarinet 1-5, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by John Clayton (Box-folder 9/20)
  - I have the feeling I've been here before, Alan Bergman / Marilyn Bergman; Vocal lead sheet; Arranged by Roger Kellaway (Box-folder 9/21)
  - I haven't got anything better to do, Score and guitar part; Arranged by Benny Carter; Small group #363 (Box-folder 34/9)
  - I just can't wait to see you, Lead sheet and parts (piano, double bass) (Box-folder 9/22)
  - I keep going back to Joe's, Jack Segal / Marvin Fisher; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/23)
  - I know you oh, so well, Dory Langdon / Ray Brown; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/24)
  - I like what I see in you, Gene DiNovi / Spence Maxwell; Parts (vocal, trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Gene DiNovi (Box-folder 9/25)
  - I like you, you're nice, Arthur King / Blossom Dearie; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/26)
  - I live to love you, Ray Gilbert / Oscar Neves; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/27)
  - I love how you love me, Stacey Dietz; Lyric sheet (Box-folder 9/28)
  - I love the life, Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone); Arranged by Arif Mardin (Box-folder 34/10)
  - I love the life I live, Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 9/29)
  - I love the life I live, Score and parts (piano/guitar, double bass, drums); Small group #401 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - I love you more than you'll ever know, Al Kooper; Parts (guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Jimmy Jones; Small group #393 (Box-folder 9/31)
  - I love you more than words will know, Al Kooper; Score and parts (strings only); Arranged by Arif Mardin (Box-folder 34/11)
  - I love you now, Christine Gardiner; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/32)
  - I love you real, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 9/33)
  - I loves you Porgy, George Gershwin / Ira Gershwin / DuBose Heyward; Parts (vocal, horn 1-3, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Small group #201 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - I mean you, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lyric sheet (Box-folder 10/1)
  - I must know, Neal Hefti / Lillian Mattis; Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/3)
  - I need you in my life, Schlosser; Parts (double bass, drums) (Box-folder 10/4)
  - I never lied to you, Gielsa Palao; Lead sheet and parts (vocal, piano, double bass, drums); Arranged by Roger Kellaway (Box-folder 10/5)
  - I never loved anyone, Lyric sheet (Box-folder 10/6)
  - I only have eyes, Parts (double bass, drums); Small group #84 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - I remember bird, Leonard Feather; Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/8)
  - I remember love, Bernie Hanighen / Tad Dameron; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 10/9)
  - I see your face, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, double bass, drums); Arranged by Ernie Wilkins (Box-folder 29/4)
  - I sold my heart to the junkman, Parts (piano, double bass) (Box-folder 10/10)
  - I sold my heart to the junkman, Score (Box-folder 29/5)
  - I thought about you, Double bass part (Box-folder 10/11)
  - I thought I knew you well, Score and parts (guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Arif Mardin (Box-folder 10/12)
  - I want you, Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, double bass); Arranged by Arif Mardin (Box-folder 10/13)
  - I will forget you, Ronnell L. Bright / Sammy Cahn; Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/14)
  - I will say goodbye, Parts (piano, double bass) (Box-folder 10/15)
  - I wish I knew, Parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-2, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Gene DiNovi; Small group #417 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - I wish I were in love, Drum part; Small group #166 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - I wish I were in love again, Richard Rodgers / Lorenz Hart; Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Nat Pierce (Box-folder 29/6)
  - I wish I were in love again, Richard Rodgers / Lorenz Hart; Score and parts (trumpet, trombone, tenor saxophone, baritone saxophone, piano/conductor, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons (Box-folder 29/7)
  - I wish you love, Score and parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #271 (Box-folder 35/1)
  - I wish you well, Bill Withers; Score, sketch, lyric sheet, parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, sop, alto saxophone, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, piano, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by Thad Jones (Box-folder 35/2)
  - I won't last a day without you, Paul Williams / Alberta Nichols; Parts (rhythm, piano, double bass, drums) (Box-folder 10/18)
  - I'd be crazy to complain, Johnny Rotella / Allen Ray; Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/19)
  - I'd rather have a memory than a dream, Leonard Feather / Jessyca Russell; Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/20)
  - If I were a bell, Parts (flute 1-2, clarinet 1-2, baritone saxophone) (Box-folder 10/21)
  - If I'm lucky, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #29 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - If love is good to me, Score and parts (conductor, vocal, oboe, piano, guitar, double bass, strings); Small group #179 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - If the moon turns green, Paul Coates / Bernie Hanighen; Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, flute, clarinet 1-4, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by John Clayton; Small group #233 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - If you could love me, Reduced score and parts (guitar, double bass); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #277 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - If you don't think I'm leaving, Johnny Rotella / Sammy Cahn; Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/26)
  - If you needed me, Peggy Lee / Dave Grusin; Lead sheet (Box-folder 10/27)
  - If you never fall in love with me, Parts (piano/guitar, double bass, drums); Small group # 140 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - I'll never pass this way again, Bob Friedman; Parts (trumpet 1-3, trombone, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone, "Flip," baritone saxophone, piano, double bass, drums, percussion); Arranged by Benny Carter (Box-folder 11/1)
  - I'll wait and pray, Gearoge Treadwill / Gerald Valentine; Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 11/2)
  - I'm all for you, Photocopied lyric sheet; Original on verso of "All too soon" lyric sheet. (Box-folder 11/3)
  - I'm alright 'til you touch me, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/4)
  - I'm always drunk in San Francisco, Tommy Wolf; Score and parts (vocal, trumpet 1-3, trombone 1-3, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, horn 1-2, harp, piano, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Benny Carter (Box-folder 35/3)
  - I'm an errand girl [boy] for rhythm, Nat King Cole; Sketch (Box-folder 11/5)
  - I'm an idiot, Don Newey; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/6)
  - I'm coming home again, Bruce Roberts / Carole Bayer Sager; Rhythm part (Box-folder 11/7)
  - I'm going back to Rio, Joáo Donato; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/8)
  - I'm gonna go back home, Redd Evans / David Mann; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/9)
  - I'm hip, Bob Dorough / Dave Frishberg; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/10)
  - I'm home, Greg Mathieson / David Frishberg; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/11)
  - I'm in a cinch to fall in love, Sidney Clare / Johnny Rotella; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/12)
  - I'm in love with the blues, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/13)
  - I'm in love with you girl, Joáo Donato / Mercedes Chies; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/14)
  - I'm just foolin' myself, Peter Tinturin / Jack Lawrence; Score and parts (trumpet, horn 1-4, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, strings); Arranged by Don Sebesky (Box-folder 29/8)
  - I'm lost, Bob Dorough; Parts (piano, guitar, double bass); Arranged by Norman Simmons; Small group #283 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - I'm shadowing you, Johnny Mercer / Blossom Dearie; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/16)
  - I'm sorry, Parts (flute 1-2, clarinet 1-2, bass cl) (Box-folder 11/17)
  - I'm through with love, Matt Malneck / Joe Livingston / Gus Kahn; Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #93 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - I'm waiting for someone, Bob Dorough; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Imagination, Piano part (Box-folder 11/20)
  - In a meditating mood, John Hendricks / Gigi Gryce; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/21)
  - In love in vain, Jerome Kern; Score and parts (vocal, trumpet, horn, harp, piano, guitar, double bass, drums, percussion, strings); Arranged by Peter Matz; Small group #45 (Box-folder 29/9)
  - In my dreams, Charles Lazar; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/22)
  - In my solitude, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #267 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - In other words, Double bass part; Small group #209 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - In the days of our love, Peggy Lee / Marian McPartland; Lead sheet (Box-folder 11/25)
  - In the lurch, Dave Brubeck / Lola Brubeck; Lyric sheet (Box-folder 11/26)
  - In Vermont, Parts (piano, double bass); Small group #101 (Box-folder 11/27)
  - In walked bud, Thelonious Monk; Parts (trumpet 1-4, trombone 1-4, alto saxophone 1-2, tenor saxophone 1-2, baritone saxophone, guitar, double bass, drums); Arranged by John Clayton (Box-folder 11/28)
  - In walked Bud, Thelonious Monk / Fred Bouchard (lyrics); Lyric sheet (Box-folder 11/29)
  - Inside a silent tear, Parts (piano, guitar) (Box-folder 11/30)
  - Invitation, Paul Francis Webster / Bronislau Kaper; Score and parts (incomplete) (piano, double bass, drums); Small group #133 (Box-folder 29/10)
  - Is it love, Lead sheet; Arranged by Norman Simmons (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Is it mad, Fran Landesman / Tommy Wolf; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Isn't it romantic, Score and parts (incomplete) (double bass, drums); Small group #169 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Isn't this a special night, Ronnell L. Bright / Sammy Cahn; Lead sheet (Box-folder 12/4)